sawwp.com 2016-01-01

# Claim Your Abundance » Privacy and Cookies Policy

SAWWP.com & Simple Fast Cash (“we”, “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We own and operate the Website.

This Privacy and Cookies Policy (together with our[ Terms of Use](http://www.simplefastcash.biz/terms-conditions/ "HOSTING Terms & Conditions") and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read this Privacy and Cookies Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

We will only use your personal data in the manner set out in this Privacy and Cookies Policy. We will only use your personal data in a way that is fair to you. We will only collect personal data where it is necessary for us to do so and where it is relevant to our dealings with you. We will only keep your personal data for as long as it is relevant to the purpose for which it was collected or for as long as we are required to keep it by law.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Simple Fast Cash with office at 49 Castleview, Tattershall, Lincoln, LN4 4JD, UK.

### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Your title, name, date of birth, address, email address, telephone numbers, username, password, business name (if applicable) and such other contact details as we require. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use the Website.
  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on the Website. This includes information provided at the time of subscribing to our services or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the Website.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

You should only submit to us or the Website information which is accurate and not misleading. You should keep that information up-to-date and let us know if any of that information changes by emailing us at [support@simplefastcash.biz](mailto:support@simplefastcash.biz). By submitting your or anyone else’s data to us or the Website, you must ensure that you have full authority and consent to supply us with that data on their behalf and you warrant to us that you have that authority.

### IP addresses

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

### Cookies

The Website uses cookies. Cookies are tiny text files which identify your computer to our server as a unique user when you visit certain pages on the Website and they are stored by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies can be used to recognise your Internet Protocol address, saving you time while you are on the Website.

We only use cookies for your convenience in using the Website and not for obtaining or using any other information about you (for example targeted advertising). Your browser can be set to not accept cookies, but this would restrict your use of the Website.

If you want to find out more information about cookies, go to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or to find out about removing them from your browser, go to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html).

Please note that we collect data from the Website about use of the Website using a web analysis tool which uses cookies that are (able to be) used to generate pseudonyms for a user’s profile. This means that use cookies (which may be stored on your computer after you leave the Website) can store information about your visit.

Please also note that our suppliers and partners may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

The Website uses the following cookies:

Name| Expiration Date| Purpose  
---|---|---  
PHPSESSID| Up to 2 years from setup/update| This cookie is used to track important logical information for the smooth operation of the site.  
pagelimit| Up to 2 years from setup/update| This cookie is used for the “Results Per Page” functionality of the client area, if you choose to use the option.  
WHMCSAffiliateID| Up to 2 years from setup/update| This cookie is used to track if you were referred to the site by an affiliate and lets us track the effectiveness of such referrals.  
WHMCSLinkID| Up to 2 years from setup/update| This cookie is used to track how you entered the site and shows us the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  
WHMCSUID  
WHMCSPW| Up to 2 years from setup/update| These cookies is used for the “Remember Me” functionality of the client area, if you choose to tick the option.  
__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz  
__utmv  
_ga| Up to 2 years from setup/update| Google Analytics cookies. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use the Website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the Website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the Website, from where visitors have come to the Website and the pages they visited once at the Website.  
  
### Where we store your personal data

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. We use industry standard security and firewalls on our servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping that password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### Security

When you make any payment to us through the Website, you must make that payment to us using PayPal or Worldpay. We do not collect any payment information from you. When submitting your payment information to PayPal or Worldpay, please note that PayPal and Worldpay each have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for those privacy policies. Please check those privacy policies before you submit any personal data to PayPal or Worldpay.

### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways and by registering you agree to these uses:

  * To ensure that content from the Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with billing information in relation to the services that we may provide to you.
  * To manage the Website, detect fraud or Website abuses, send you information relevant to the Website and in case we have any queries.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To notify you about changes to our services.
  * To allow you to register for an account on the Website, which may include sending an email to you to confirm your details.
  * To give you a new password if you have forgotten it.
  * To keep you updated regarding information relating to your account
  * To allow your upline and/or downline to contact you
  * To allow you to contact your downline
  * To allow you to contact your sponsor

We also need to use your contact details and other information for any aspect of the Website (including, without limitation, providing customer support, preventing or investigating prohibited activity, enforcing the [Terms of Use](http://www.simplefastcash.biz/terms-conditions/ "HOSTING Terms & Conditions") and verifying information).

We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business or part of it to an actual or potential purchaser.

We may also disclose your details as described elsewhere in this Privacy and Cookies Policy.

Other than as set out in this Privacy and Cookies Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy and Cookies Policy or unless we are required to do so by law.

### Other websites

The Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of Â£10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Consent

By submitting data to us and using the Website, you consent to our use of your data and of anyone you represent in the manner set out in this Privacy and Cookies Policy (as amended from time to time, as described below) and you are responsible for ensuring that you have authority to consent on behalf of anyone about whom you submit data to us.

Please note that you can revoke any consent you have given us under this policy at any time by contacting us on support@simplefastcash.biz, and referencing this Privacy and Cookies Policy in the email subject line, using the body of the email to say what consent you are revoking.

### Changes to our Privacy and Cookies Policy

Any changes we may make to this Privacy and Cookies Policy in the future will be posted on the Website and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Each time you enter the Website, you agree that the Privacy and Cookies Policy current at that time shall apply to all information held by you.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy and Cookies Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to support@simplefastcash.biz.

This Privacy Policy was most recently updated on 20th September 2013.
